[Music]
foreign
there's no doubt that time is passing
very fast it's been 35 years since the
first Predator movie was released and
this year we already saw its fifth part
everything started in the rainforest of
Vietnam and after that a legendary movie
franchise was born four years after the
alien creatures last landed on Earth
we've watched a new Predator movie that
maybe will become the best and it seems
that another one is coming so stay with
us and find out first let's make a
little recap of what happened this
August it was a prequel story in the
first four movies and it was set in the
Northern Great Plains in North America
in 1719. the movie that was named prey
is currently streaming on Disney Plus in
the UK in Hulu in the US prey is very
worthwhaji as the first impressions of
the audience are very fascinating set in
the 18th century the movie tells the
story of nauru a skilled Comanche
Warrior who protects her tribe from the
Predator that has dropped down from the
sky the premiere of the movie happened
at the San Diego Comic Con on July 21
2022 and was released by 20th century
Studios even though before the premiere
the movie was criticized for the cast
section which was composed of many
unknown names the film is now receiving
only positive reviews from critics with
praise especially for the action
sequences praise for the leading
actresses performance Amber mid Thunder
and also for the relatively young
director Dan trattenberg many critics
even say that prey is already the best
Predator installment since the first
film and what makes this film so special
simply it has a great story in it gray
showed you that you don't need to have a
big budget to achieve great goals the
movie managed to achieve a 7.2 rating on
IMDb in a fantastic 77 audience score on
Rotten Tomatoes only one month after the
premiere for example the Predator from
2018 was a big budget attempt to revive
the frame franchise and bring it back on
the throne but it turned out to be only
a critical and financial dud the newest
Predator movie went back to what made
the original Predator movie work the
fight between nauru with a so-called
feral Predator who comes to Earth
seeking worthy trophies is characterized
as good as the first Predator movie with
Arnold Schwarzenegger Jesse Ventura and
Carl Weathers in the leading roles these
legendary actors are the real culprits
who hit that like button just like you
should if you haven't done so already no
really these actors are the real
culprits who made Predator story so
popular and one of the longest living
movie franchise on the big screens after
this legendary presentation of the story
in front of the audience we watched
three sequels the alien creature came
again in 1990 in Predator 2 and again in
2010 in predators and the last one we
already mentioned was the Predator from
2018. this franchise also included two
movie Specialties Alien vs Predator in
Alien vs Predator Requiem in 2004 and
2007. in total the movies grossed over
750 million dollars at the end of the
last movie prey everything was left open
and many Mysteries still need to be
exposed including the one about the gun
leaving a very wide open door for a
possible sequel let's see if there is
any potential release date for the prey
sequel the development of prey started
even before the premiere of 2018's The
Predator when the director trottenberg
approached the producer John Davis and
met a win the concept on which he has
been working on since 2016. then in 2020
the film title was revealed which was
also criticized because there were four
other movies in the past with the same
name there is a German survival Thriller
a horror movie prey from 2019. one
that's Spanish from the same year and
also Norman J Warren's movie prey from
1977. the filming for the fifth Predator
installment took place in Calgary Canada
during this summer of 2021 and it was
wrapped by September now fans of the
franchise are constantly asking if there
will be a sequel for the prequel story
to clear things up the film producer
John Davis recently in an interview
confirmed that he does have plans for a
possible sequel or a possible Predator 6
movie so after prey succeeded in just a
month to revive the franchise things
seem to be very bright for the future
some leaks are saying that in the case
of a renewal the release date for the
prey sequel will be known at the
earliest in mid of 2024. now let's see
if there is any information about who
may return to reprise their roles in the
potential six Predator movie the cast
crew and prey was maybe not so familiar
to the audience but they surely were
aware of the burden they had to carry
for this kind of movie franchise the
young but extra talented Amber mid
Thunder was playing the main role of
nauru Dan delegriot who is a former
basketball player was wearing the
clothes of the predator and stormy Kip
who became known to the audience from
the movie sui played fellow Comanche
Warrior Wasabi we also saw the musician
Dakota beavers as the Comanche Warchief
Toddy and Stephanie Matthias as the
chief wife Sumo we know that the
Predator killed Wasabi and the war chief
tabi so they probably won't come back to
reprise their roles a lot of other
Comanche warriors were killed in the
fight with the mighty creature we can't
be sure who is and who is not coming
back to reprise their role but it's sure
that now is the right time for you to
smash that subscribe button and hit that
notification Bell below the video no
really it's almost sure that we will see
some new faces if the sequel of prey is
going to happen there are a lot of
Native American actors that could join
the cast if the movie stays in the same
period last but not least let's see what
we can expect from the story in the
potential sixth film The Predator films
had some strange Journey since the
original was released with many rotating
protagonists said settings and enemies
the last movie was another one in the
sequence of these twists in the
scenarios the longtime producer of The
Predator movies John Davis who has been
involved in the franchise since the
first movie in 1987. recently for
variety commented on the success of prey
and he also commented on the
possibilities for future adaptations
Davis said that the creatures could
appear in every period Well maybe
there's an origin story right maybe
there's another Alien vs Predator story
in a different situation and maybe
there's a new modern day version and
maybe there's something somewhere in
between I think this character can show
up throughout history he said on the
other side director tritenberg more
precisely a seat that he is open to the
idea of a new movie in an interview with
time out he said there are a lot of
exciting ideas for what could be for the
next franchise the things that most
excite me are the bodus wings and I
think there's scope to do other things
that haven't been done before if you
analyze these comments you will conclude
that it seems the Predator franchise
will continue in some other ambient in
some other period but still the end
credits of prey suggest that the Saga
will continue with a sequel at the end
of the movie the young Warrior girl will
use the Predator's technology to kill
the creature she will return to her
tribe with a predator's head and will
celebrate with her people but she will
urge them that they must react quickly
because out there is still a threat
maybe she thinks about the French
Trapper she met before and killed some
of them but we know that this Predator
is not the last of its kind as the story
happens in 1719 and we already know that
the creatures who are hungry for human
trophies will also show up in modern
times so guys stay patient because very
soon we will know how the Saga will
continue the story and the producers
will probably wait a few more months to
analyze the success of their recently
released movie and then the answers will
come thanks for watching we'll see you
next time
foreign